<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Pragya Reads!!</title>
    <link href="https://pragya42.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://pragya42.github.io" />
    <updated>2021-09-18T01:27:29+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Pragya Jatav</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://pragya42.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>tst</title>
        <author>
            <name>Pragya Jatav</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://pragya42.github.io/tst/"/>
        <id>https://pragya42.github.io/tst/</id>
            <category term="Poetry"/>
            <category term="Fantasy"/>

        <updated>2021-09-18T01:27:29+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://pragya42.github.io/media/posts/4/test-3.jpg" alt="" />
                    WFBOHJNWjbfjebfjqebjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjj
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://pragya42.github.io/media/posts/4/test-3.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>WFBOHJNWjbfjebfjqebjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjj</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>TBR</title>
        <author>
            <name>Pragya Jatav</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://pragya42.github.io/tbr/"/>
        <id>https://pragya42.github.io/tbr/</id>

        <updated>2021-09-18T01:20:18+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://pragya42.github.io/media/posts/3/poem1.jpg" alt="" />
                     Night Watch 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://pragya42.github.io/media/posts/3/poem1.jpg" alt="" />
                <ul>
<li>Night Watch</li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wuthering Heights by Emily Bronte</title>
        <author>
            <name>Pragya Jatav</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://pragya42.github.io/wuthering-heights-by-emily-bronte/"/>
        <id>https://pragya42.github.io/wuthering-heights-by-emily-bronte/</id>
            <category term="Classic Lit"/>

        <updated>2021-09-18T00:04:32+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://pragya42.github.io/media/posts/1/test-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    I won't really call this a review, because I am more confused&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://pragya42.github.io/media/posts/1/test-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>I won't really call this a review, because I am more confused about it than I was the last time I read the book. This book will leave you (or it left me) utterly devastated, lonely and hateful. Not to mention confused. It is a beautifully written book though.  It shines while depicting complicated emotions. And the dialogue! Even though I don't care for a single character in this story, I listen when they talk. Also, the setting  Wuthering heights and Thushcross Grange and the moor is so great. I have way too many tinfoily theories about that place. The only character I have strong feelings about is Nelly and I hate her. There is a huge conversation about her being the unreliable narrator too. And I really liked where Catherine ended up. Not the state but the place. Trying really hard to be spoiler-free. I think I need more time and re-reads to make conversation about the themes of trauma and love etc. in this book. To be honest, I don't know what I read, but it did make me feel extremely agitated, so I guess it's truly good literature. As a good piece of literature is supposed to make you feel heightened emotions. That's not me! Plato said it. Also, I don't think he meant it in a positive way. All I can say for sure is that it's a classic and everyone should experience it at least once. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
